<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Group_Portfolio_HW_Team_Alpha</string>
    <!--Enrique's Portfolio Texts-->
    <string name="enrique_name">Enrique CRUZ</string>
    <string name="enrique_biography">Born in January 11, 1994, I was born and raised in Brooklyn NY. My mother and father are devoted parents who
        have done a lot to raise me and without them I wouldn\'t be where I am at now. I enjoy coding and receiving more knowledge when not in class or at
        work. In the meantime when I am not studying I enjoy playing video games as well as playing with my kitten who helps relax me.</string>
    <string name="enrique_project1">Mad Libs</string>
    <string name="enrique_project2">Bank Teller</string>
    <string name="enrique_project3">Adventure Game</string>
    <!--Menu Names-->
    <string name="enrique_menu">Enrique\'s Portfolio</string>
    <string name="talha_menu">Talha\'s Portfolio</string>
    <string name="cliff_menu">Clifford\'s Portfolio</string>
    <string name="elizabeth_menu">Elizabeth\'s Portfolio</string>
    <!--Activity_main's Portfolio Texts-->
    <string name="title_main"> The goal of this application : </string>
    <string name="goal_text_view"> Life gives us methods… we pass in the arguments.
        We are a group of creative and talented individuals eager to unlock our potential
        in the tech world. Although we come from different branches of life, we pushed ourselves
        to commit to this master branch despite the conflicts we faced. Who knows where the
        future will take us, but for now we are in this programming journey together -
        and best believe Group Alpha is ready for the challenge!</string>
    <!--Elizabeth's Portfolio Texts-->
    <string name="elizabeth_biography">My name is Elizabeth and I am an Android Developer fellow at Pursuit.
        I was born in Seoul, South Korea, moved to States when I was 14 years old. I used to live in Seattle and Los Angeles before I moved to NYC.
        After spending nearly a decade working in Interior Design, I decided to change her career in IT. I am passionate about Art,
        Design, and Travel. My hobbies are going to art museums and painting.</string>
    <string name="elizabeth_project1">EY Restaurant</string>
    <string name="elizabeth_project2">Java Bank</string>
    <string name="elizabeth_project3">Android Story App</string>
    <string name="elizabeth_name">Elizabeth YU</string>
    <!--Clifford's Portfolio Texts-->
    <string name="clifford_name">Clifford CHARLES</string>
    <string name="cliff_biography">Cliff is up and coming software developer with great attention
        to detail and the user experience. Always learning and improving, he is interested in seamlessly blending tech
        into everyday modern life. Cliff is also invested in skateboarding, boxing, and video games. You can catch him still putting in work while dying in the hospital.
        A 6ft tall monster. Straight beast.</string>
    <string name="cliff_project1">Banking Terminal</string>
    <string name="cliff_project2">Mad Libs</string>
    <string name="cliff_project3">Pursuit Homework</string>
    <!--Talha's Portfolio Texts-->
    <string name="talha_name">Talha RAHMAN</string>
    <string name="talha_biography">My name is Talha and I am an aspiring Android developer here at Pursuit. As a native New Yorker,
        I have a genuine curiosity in exploring different cultures and neighborhoods and am always surprised at the new things I discover.
        I am interested in understanding and trying to solve different problems, and in particular I plan to work on transportation systems to
        help move and improve the lives of everyday people in cities like New York.</string>
    <string name="talha_project1">Adventure Game</string>
    <string name="talha_project2">Java Bank</string>
    <string name="talha_project3">Android Story App</string>
    <!--Navigation Menu texts-->
    <string name="title_activity_navigation_menu">NavigationMenu</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Portfolios</string>
</resources>
